bestdesignoptions.com 2011-06-19

# The Best Design Options for Designers and Everyone Else | Best Design Options

If you are looking for great design resources, tutorials, tips and inspiration you have come to the right place. Best Design Options is a site dedicated to providing you with the best design-related materials that you can use for free. You can also find here design examples and inspiration just in case you badly need one if you have the so-called “creative block” which every designer experiences once in a while. To help you navigate around this site, please refer to the CATEGORY listing found on the right sidebar. However, below are some quick links to the many resources you can find from this site:

[PHOTOSHOP RESOURCES ](http://bestdesignoptions.com/?cat=26 "photoshop resources")(Tutorials, Brushes, Templates, Textures, Patterns)

Stay tuned for freebies such as business card templates for personal and professional, photoshop brushes, textures, patterns, website templates, themes and many more that we are going to give away via this blog as well as the tips, tutorials and other expert advice that we will try to assemble in this blog.

**Privacy Policy for www.bestdesignoptions.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@bestdesignoptions.com.

At www.bestdesignoptions.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.bestdesignoptions.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.bestdesignoptions.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.bestdesignoptions.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.bestdesignoptions.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.bestdesignoptions.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.bestdesignoptions.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.bestdesignoptions.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.bestdesignoptions.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**DISCLAIMER**

This internet site is presented for the purpose of disseminating information only. This public domain monitors the quality of the information available on this internet site and updates the information regularly. This public domain does not, however, guarantee the accuracy, reliability, currency, completeness of any material contained on the site, including all personal information uploaded to the site by its users. Furthermore, this internet site will not be accountable for any legal liability that may arise from any material contained on this internet site or on any linked site. This internet site is not a substitute for independent professional advice and users should obtain any appropriate professional advice relevant to their particular circumstances. The material on this internet site may include the views or recommendations of third parties, which do not necessarily reflect the views of this site, or indicate its commitment to a particular course of action.

This entry was posted on Wednesday, January 7th, 2009 at 8:20 pm and is filed under [Blogging Tips](http://bestdesignoptions.com/?category_name=blogging-tips "View all posts in Blogging Tips"). You can follow any responses to this entry through the [RSS 2.0](http://bestdesignoptions.com/?feed=rss2&p=6) feed.
